alextnj.com · +46 70 748 38 97

PRESENTATION

Studied Computer Engineering at KTH where I acquired a versatile skill set and knowledge of IT and programming, along with experience of collaborative software development both on a large and a small scale. In addition to my studies, I have gained deeper knowledge of web application development with several years of experience coding in the full stack with various languages, frameworks, and libraries.

EDUCATION

Computer Engineering KTH, Royal Institute of Technology 5 years

CS50's Web Programming Harvard University MOOC Course 12 weeks

Chemical Engineering KTH, Royal Institute of Technology 1 year

WORK EXPERIENCE

2022–2024 Heartstart AB Instructor

Instructor and educator for CPR both theoretically and practically. Also participated in creating educational materials.

2021–2023 IMT Sweden AB Machine Technician

Assembled, disassembled, and performed mechanical and electrical maintenance on automated garbage collection machines.

2021 KTH, Royal Institute of Technology Teaching Assistant Assisted students in laboratory and project work in the courses Digital Design and Embedded Systems.

2019–2020 Studybuddy AB Private Tutor

Private tutor for elementary and high school students in mathematics, physics, and chemistry.

2016–2018 Premo, Pressen Morgontjänst KB Newspaper Distributor

Distributed newspapers to apartments and houses at night by car.

SKILLS

Programming Languages

Java, JavaScript, TypeScript, Python, GDScript, C, ASM, Elixir, Bash

Frameworks & Libraries

Angular, React, React Native, Redux, Next.js, jQuery, Bootstrap, Tailwind, Express.js, Java Spring, Python Flask & Django

Database Technologies

MySQL, PostgreSQL, MongoDB (with mongoose), Redis

Other

AWS, Docker, Nginx, Node.js, GraphQL, Linux (Debian based & Arch), GIT, Postman, HTML, CSS

OTHER

Fluent in Swedish and English Intermediate Spanish Swedish Driving License